#### Curriculum Vitae

# **Duccio AIAZZI**

GIS & Urban Data Analysis

I am a data analyst with a specialisation in urban and geo-tagged data and skills in GIS and spatial analysis, obtained at the Centre for Advanced Spatial Analysis, at UCL. I have a background in architecture with a long experience in the problematics of the city and in urban and architectural design. Having a hybrid professional profile, I can deal with complex issues related to multiple fields such as data science, urban planning, data visualisation and web technology. I have a personal inclination towards technical tasks but I aim at a good balance between technical work and management.

name: Duccio surname: Aiazzi nationality: Italian

date of birth: April 2, 1978
address: 33 rue Fondary, Paris 75015
email: duccio.aiazzi@gmail.com
web: whatforlunch.duccioaiazzi.com tel: +33 (0) 7 60 15 87 59

tel: +33 (0) 7 60 15 87 59

driving license: European B

### Education

2016	UCL, Centre for Advanced Spatial Analysis CASA	London	MSc "Smart Cities and Urban Analytics"	Distinction
2014	John Hopkins University	MOOC on coursera.org	Data Science Specialization	
2009	London Metropolitan University	London	MSc "Architecture, Energy and Sustainability"	Distinction
2005	Universita degli Studi di Firenze	Firenze	Bachelor in Architecture	Distinction

## Work Experience (2006-2017)

2016-2017	GIS and Data analyst consultant	London	Data analysis and visualisation, free-lance consultant
2015	Reichen et Robert & Associes	Paris	Architect
2013-2014	SoA Architectes	Paris	Architect
2012-2013	Atelier Zundel Cristea	Paris	Architect, Project Leader
2007-2011	Sheppard Robson	London	Architect, Project leader
2006-2007	Ttsp	London	Architect
2002-2006	Miranda Ferrara Architects	Italy	Student architect

#### Competences

Italian	++++	Mother-tongue
English	++++	Level C2
French	<b>+++</b> \$	Level C1
Python	<b>**</b> *	Writing functions, Data cleaning and analysis, visualisation, interaction with PostgreSQL and PostGIS, API queries.
R	<b>+++</b> \$	Writing optimised functions, data cleaning and analysis, static and interactive visualisation, API queries.
PostgreSQL	<b>**</b> *	
PostGIS	<b>+++</b> \$	
JavaScript / HTML	<b>***</b>	Writing and editing of basic static or interactive web pages
Adobe Suite	++++	Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign
CAD	++++	AutoCAD, Microstation, Sketchup

# Other skills

Network analysis

Spatial Point Pattern Analysis

Spatial auto-correlation, local test, global test Clustering and classification techniques (DBscan, k-means)

Spatio-temporal series analysis

Basic understanding of basic machine learning (SVG, Random Forest)